Leo Ng

Work permit through E-3 Visa / NO SPONSORSHIP REQUIRED

Mobile: +61 432 869 228 Email: leonard.leo.ng@outlook.com LinkedIn Profile

CORE SKILLS

Relationship building skills: I am a people-person at heart. I build great relationships in both my personal and professional life. I have a consistent client retention record and this is the first time I've had to use a resume since 2011! The last two times I got pulled over, I made friends with the police officers and got one of them on Facebook! Link

Strong technical aptitude: I enjoy understanding technical and complex things thoroughly. Combined with my relationship skills, I have a strong sales ability and capacity to train people. I have implemented highly-customized software for hundreds of clients, lead developers and have a penchant for understanding the technical details.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Inspection Express, Business Development / Account Manager, September 2015 - Current

Start-up, providing software to Australian real estate industry, est. 2013

- ➤ Maintained 100% client retention of assigned clients
- Advise Owner/Director on strategy, including identifying opportunities for business/product development
- Identified unmet demand for software to streamline client's common admin tasks leading to subsequent launch of new Paperless Condition Reporting (PCR) service.
- Revised Director's workflow and user experience for PCR service to ensuring minimal future support needs
- Developed and solely produced campaign video for launch of PCR, including script and storyboard writing, voiceover and animation [Link here]

Inspect Real Estate, Distributor, October 2014 – August 2016

Fast-growing start-up providing online booking / CRM software to Australian real estate industry, est. 2011

- Implemented software for 71 new clients, accumulating \$1.3M annual revenue for the business
- Maintained 96%+ client retention rate, losing only three. Two losses due to client insolvency.
- Tied 1st place for internal national sales competition in February 2016 for number of new clients signed
- Full Sales Process from lead generation by cold calling, email marketing & door knocking to presenting, signing, full on-site software implementation and training across four states
- Provide responsive customer support and ongoing software customization
- Liaise between clients and development team on technical issues to ensure resolution

1Form, Client Services Manager, October 2011 – March 2014

Successful start-up providing Australia's industry-standard Online Tenancy Application. Acquired by REA Group 2014.

- Performed over 500 online sales/training demonstrations to prospective clients
- > Performed presentations to audiences of 500+ at various trade shows across Australia
- Managed Key Relationships, our highest-level accounts ensuring client retention
- Transitioned myself from sole support contact to hiring and training our offshore Client Services Team
- Managed Client Services Team, encompassing support, account management and sales roles.
- Raised company customer service perceptions from terrible to excellent, which greatly assisted 1Form's sale to REA Group upon customer satisfaction audit.
- Created detailed documentation, specifications and UI requirements for new backend portal for Client Services Team and subsequent REA Group Customer Service Team.
- Managed successful transition of knowledge, procedures and accounts to REA Group upon acquisition in 2014. REA Group Customer Service Team members able to resolve 90%+ issues without development support

Carsales.com.au, Data Operations Analyst, February 2011 – August 2011 (6-month contract role)

Australia's No.1 automotive portal. Equivalent of Autotrader / eBay Motors in Australia.

- Performed market analysis on Australian car industry, correlating web traffic data with vehicle purchase trends
- Lead project to create complete dataset by combining incomplete DMV data with vehicle sales listings
- Hired and coached staff to manually cleanse dataset, ensuring consistent, high quality data

EDUCATION

Deloitte Innovation Fastrack Program, 2010

RMIT University, School of Management, Bachelor of Business (Entrepreneurship), Graduated 2010 Babson College, Spring 2010 exchange program, one of two RMIT students selected.

WORK ELIGIBILITY

I am an Australian Citizen eligible to work in the USA through the E-3 immigration program. This program allows US companies to easily hire Australians at <u>no financial cost and only requires the employer to submit one form</u> to the Department of Labor, and approval is usually given within 14 days. <u>More info here</u>.